<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<About>
  <App Title="Weatherman"
       Author="Matt McCormick"
       Description=""
       Publisher=""
       AdditionalNotes="This application uses the Forecast.io application programming interface but is not endorsed or certified by Dark Sky Company, LLC.\n\nSwipe right to left for legal notices." />
  <Items>
    <MainItem Title="about"
              AppAuthorLabel="by"
              AppDescriptionLabel=""
              AppPublisherLabel=""
              AppVersionLabel="Version:"
              AppAdditionalNotesLabel="Additional Notes:"
              AppReviewButtonContent="review this app">
      <Links>
        <Link NavigateUri="http://mbmccormick.com"
              Content="http://mbmccormick.com"
              Label="Website:" />
        <Link NavigateUri="mailto:feedback@mbmccormick.com"
              Content="feedback@mbmccormick.com"
              Label="Support:" />
      </Links>
    </MainItem>
    <Item Title="legal" Type="text">
      Privacy Policy
      Weatherman is a client application designed for connecting you with the excellent Forecast.io service. Note that by using the Forecast.io service, you also are likely bound by their terms of service (available at https://developer.forecast.io/terms_of_use.txt) as well as their privacy policy (available at http://forecast.io/privacy.html). This policy is additive to that of the Forecast.io privacy policy, since Weatherman is only a client application.

      Information Collected
      In the event of an application error, crash, or problem, we may ask you to send an email message with crash information. Such an email may contain personally identifiable information, and it is your choice whether to send such a message. While using the app, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and help you resolve support or assistance with the app. This will happen through a prompt asking for feedback, allowing you to send an e-mail message, and is not automatic. In order to provide you with a better experience, to improve the application and its services, we may share non-identifying information (such as the current page within the application being viewed) to serve you better and analyze and understand how the app is used.

      Notes
      Forecast.io is a trademark of Dark Sky Company, LLC. This application uses the Forecast.io application programming interface but is not endorsed or certified by Dark Sky Company, LLC.

      Contacting the Author
      If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to feedback@mbmccormick.com.

    </Item>
    <Item Title="what's new?" Type="text">
      Version 1.0
      This is the first release of Weatherman and contains the basic features provided by Forecast.io and fully integrates with the Windows Phone experience.

    </Item>
  </Items>
</About>

